HARBOR FREIGHT PRIVACY POLICY
=============================

**Last Updated: February 14, 2024**

Harbor Freight respects your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect, how we use the information, with whom we may share it and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information. We also describe measures we take to protect the security of the information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.

If you are a California consumer, please see the section of this Privacy Policy called “[California Privacy Statement](#caPrivacyStatement)” for more information about your privacy rights.

Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:

Information We Obtain
---------------------

We obtain personal information about you in various ways, such as when you visit our website or use our mobile app (collectively, the “Services”). We also may obtain personal information about you offline, such as when you call one of Harbor Freight’s Customer Call Centers, mail or fax us, or interact with us at one of our stores. The types of personal information we may obtain include:

* Contact information, such as name, telephone number and postal and email address;
* Account information, such as login information, screen name, account preferences and other account details;
* Billing information, including name and billing and delivery address;
* Payment card details, which are collected by our third-party payment processor on our behalf;
* Purchase history;
* The geolocation of your device if you provide us with permission to collect this data;
* Information provided when you request funding or a donation, or you submit a nomination directly from the “[Harborfreightgivingback.com](https://harborfreightgivingback.com/)” Site; and
* Other information you choose to provide, such as through emails or other communications, social media pages, surveys, registrations and sign-up forms.

When you use our Services or open our emails, we may obtain certain information by automated means, such as cookies, pixel tags, server or device logs, session replay and screen capture technology, and other technologies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “pixel tag” (also known as a web beacon), which is a type of technology that is often used in combination with cookies, is placed on a website or within an email to track certain activity, such as views of a website or when an email is opened. These technologies help us (1) remember your information so you do not have to re-enter it; (2) track and understand how you use and interact with the Services; (3) tailor the Services around your preferences; (4) measure the usability of the Services and the effectiveness of our communications; (5) authenticate your identity, protect against fraud and provide our products and services; and (6) otherwise manage and enhance our products and services, and help ensure they are working properly.

We also may use session replay and screen capture technology to collect, on a real-time basis, information on how you use and navigate the Services. This may include mouse movements, how you scroll through the Services, and certain keystroke information.

We may use these automated technologies on the Services to collect information about your device, browsing actions, and usage patterns. We obtain information about your device and web browser in this manner such as your device IP address, general location information, unique device identifiers, device type and model, device characteristics and settings, browser settings and characteristics, operating system type and version, language and country preferences, battery and signal strength, usage statistics, referring emails and web addresses, and other application details. We also may obtain information about your interactions with our Services, such as pages visited, links clicked, features used, dates and times of usage, session information, and other information about your use of our Services.

Your browser may tell you how to be notified about certain types of automated collection technologies and how to restrict or disable them. Please note, however, that without these technologies, you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services. For mobile devices, you can manage how your device and browser share certain device data by adjusting the privacy and security settings on your mobile device.

How We Use the Information We Obtain
------------------------------------

We may use the personal information we obtain to:

* Provide our products and services, manage your accounts, process your orders, ensure proper delivery, process returns, better assist you when you visit or call us as well as to improve our product and service offerings;
* Communicate with you, respond to inquiries and offer customer support;
* Personalize your experience with our products and services;
* Advertise and market our products and services;
* Administer participation in surveys, sweepstakes, promotions or other programs;
* Perform analytics and market, trend or statistical research;
* Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; improving and analyzing our products and services; managing our communications; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions);
* Maintain and enhance the safety and security of our products and services, prevent misuse and troubleshoot technical issues;
* Verify your identity and protect against fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities;
* Exercise our rights and remedies and defend against legal claims; and
* Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and Harbor Freight policies, including Harbor Freight’s [Terms & Conditions](https://www.harborfreight.com/terms-and-conditions).

We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

### _Third-Party Analytics Services_

We may use third-party analytics services on the Services, such as Google Analytics. We also may use third-party session replay and screen capture services that record users’ interactions with the Services. The providers of these analytics services use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, session replay and screen capture technology, and similar automated technologies to help us analyze your use of the Services. The information collected through these means may be disclosed to or collected directly by these services. To learn more about Google Analytics, please visit [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

### _Interest-Based Advertising_

You may see our ads on other websites because we use third-party ad services on our Services. Through these ad services, we can tailor our messaging to individuals considering demographic data, inferred interests and browsing context. These ad services track information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites and apps by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs, web beacons and other similar technologies. These ad services may collect data about your visits to websites and apps that participate in these services, such as the pages or ads you view and the actions you take on the websites or apps. This data collection takes place both on our Services and on third-party websites and apps that participate in these ad services. These ad services use this information to show you ads that may be tailored to your individual interests. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. Our Services are not designed to respond to “do not track” signals from browsers.

To learn how to opt out of interest-based advertising in the U.S., please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices), [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), and [http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/).

Information We Share
--------------------

We may share the categories of personal information we obtain about you (as described above) with the categories of third parties listed in this section. We may share the information we obtain about you with our affiliated companies. We may share your personal information with third-parties so that they may provide you with information about our products and services and special offers. We also may share the information we obtain about you with third-party vendors and other entities to perform services on our behalf, such as delivery providers, technology and communications providers, payment processing and billing service providers, advertising and marketing service providers, and others. We may share your personal information with social media platforms if you use those services to connect with us.

We may disclose personal information (1) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (2) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; (3) to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights; (4) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical or other harm or financial loss; (5) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity or (6) otherwise with your consent or as directed by your representative.

In addition, we reserve the right to transfer to relevant third parties the personal information we have about you in the event of a potential or actual sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a merger, acquisition, joint venture, reorganization, divestiture, dissolution, or liquidation), or other business transaction.

Personal Information gathered solely from the “[Harborfreightgivingback.com](https://harborfreightgivingback.com/)” Site may also be shared with The Smidt Foundation, Harbor Freight Tools for Schools, LLC, Harbor Freight Tools Foundation, LLC, and each of their respective affiliates.

Your Rights and Choices
-----------------------

We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information we collect from you. To update your preferences, limit the communications you receive from us, or submit a request, please contact us as indicated in the [How To Contact Us](#contactUs) section of this Privacy Policy. You can unsubscribe from our marketing mailing lists by following the “Unsubscribe” link in our emails. If you choose not to use that link or did not receive a Promotional email from Harbor Freight, you may send an email request to [cs@harborfreight.com](mailto:cs@harborfreight.com?subject=REMOVE) with the word “REMOVE” in the subject line and your email address in the body. You also may update certain of your account details and settings by logging into your account on the Services.

If you are a California resident, please see the [California Privacy Statement](#caPrivacyStatement) section of this Privacy Policy for more information about your privacy rights.

If you are a Colorado resident, please see the [Colorado Consumer Privacy Statement](#coPrivacyStatement) section of this Privacy Policy for more information about your privacy rights.

If you are a Connecticut, Utah or Virginia resident, you may have the right to: (1) request access to, or correction or deletion of, your personal information; or (2) opt out of the processing of your personal information for purposes of targeted advertising or the sale of your personal information. To request access to, correction of or deletion of your personal data, please click [here](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f). To opt-out of the processing of your personal data for purposes of targeted advertising or the sale of your personal data, go to the footer of our website and select the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information / Opt Out of Targeted Advertising” link, or click [here](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f).

You may appeal our decision with respect to a request you have submitted by sending an email to: [privacy@harborfreight.com](mailto:privacy@harborfreight.com?subject=Consumer%20Rights%20Appeal) with “Consumer Rights Appeal” in the subject line (must be sent from the email address used to make the Consumer Rights request).

How We Protect Personal Information
-----------------------------------

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect personal information against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized access, destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure or use.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

The Services are designed for a general audience and are not directed to children. In connection with the Services, we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will either seek parental consent or promptly delete that information. If you believe that a child under age 13 may have provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us as specified in the [How To Contact Us](#contactUs) section of this Privacy Policy.

Links to Third-Party Services and Features
------------------------------------------

For your convenience and information, the Services may provide links to other online services (such as websites or social media platforms), and may include third-party features such as apps, tools, widgets and plug-ins. These online services and third-party features may operate independently from us. The privacy practices of the relevant third parties, including details on the information they may collect about you, are subject to the privacy statements of these parties, which we strongly suggest you review. To the extent any linked online services or third-party features are not owned or controlled by Harbor Freight, we are not responsible for these third parties’ information practices.

Updates to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will indicate at the top of the policy when it was most recently updated.

How to Contact Us
-----------------

You can update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, submit a request or ask us questions about this Privacy Policy by contacting us at:

1. Send an email to: [cs@harborfreight.com](mailto:cs@harborfreight.com?subject=Internet%20Customer%20Service) with “Internet Customer Service” in the subject line
2. Call [1-800-444-3353](tel:1-800-444-3353) Monday thru Friday, 5:00am-5:00pm PT and Saturday & Sunday, 7:00am- 3:00pm PT.
3. Send your request by mail to:
    
    Harbor Freight Tools  
    PO Box 6010  
    Camarillo, CA 93011  
    ATTN: Internet Customer Service

California Consumer Privacy Statement
-------------------------------------

Last Updated: **January 1st, 2023**

This California Privacy Statement supplements the Privacy and Security Policy. It applies solely to California residents, except for Harbor Freight personnel, and addresses personal information we collect online and offline.

This Statement uses certain terms that have the meaning given to them in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020) and its implementing regulations (collectively, the “CCPA/CPRA”).

**1\. Notice of Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We may collect (and may have collected during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Statement) the following categories of personal information about you:

* **Identifiers:** identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier (such as a device identifier; cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers and similar technology; customer number, unique pseudonym, or user alias; telephone number and other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers), online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, Social Security number, driver's license number, passport number, and other similar identifiers
* **Additional Data Subject to Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80:** signature, physical characteristics or description, state identification card number, education, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, other financial information, medical information, and health insurance information
* **Protected Classifications:** characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as race, color, national origin, religion, age, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, marital status, medical condition, ancestry, disability, citizenship status, and military and veteran status
* **Commercial Information:** commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, and other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
* **Online Activity:** Internet and other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with websites, applications or advertisements
* **Geolocation Data**
* **Sensory Information:** audio, electronic, visual, and similar information
* **Employment Information:** professional or employment-related information
* **Education Information:** education information that is not publicly available personally identifiable information as defined in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Sec. 1232g; 34 C.F.R. Part 99)
* **Inferences:** inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes

We may use (and may have used during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Statement) your personal information for the purposes described in our Privacy & Security Policy and for the following business purposes specified in the CCPA/CPRA:

* Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing analytics services, providing storage or providing similar services
* Providing advertising and marketing services to you, except for cross-context behavioral advertising (which is addressed in Section 5 of this Statement)
* Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance
* Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising shown as part of your current interaction with us
* Helping to ensure security and integrity, to the extent the use of your personal information is reasonably necessary and proportionate for these purposes
* Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality
* Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration
* Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us
* Managing career opportunities with Harbor Freight.

**2\. Collection and Use of Sensitive Personal Information**

We do not collect or use (and have not collected or used during the 12 month period prior to the effective date of this Statement) “sensitive personal information,” as defined under the CCPA/CPRA.

**3\. Retention of Personal Information**

We will retain your personal information for the time period reasonably necessary to achieve the purposes described in our Privacy and Security Policy and this Statement, or any other notice provided at the time of data collection, taking into account applicable statutes of limitation and records retention requirements under applicable law, as well as our records retention requirements and policies.

**4\. Sources of Personal Information**

During the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Statement, we may have obtained personal information about you from the following categories of sources:

* Directly from you, such as when you make a purchase
* From your devices, such as when you visit our Sites
* Our affiliates and subsidiaries
* Vendors who provide services on our behalf
* Online advertising services and advertising networks
* Data analytics providers
* Government entities
* Social networks
* Data brokers
* Recruiting and talent agencies
* Job references

**5\. Sale or Sharing of Personal Information**

We do not exchange your personal information for monetary consideration. We may allow certain third parties (such as online advertising services and social networks) to collect your personal information via automated technologies on our Sites for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes. Under California law, these kinds of disclosures may be considered a “sale” when the personal information is exchanged for non-monetary consideration, or “sharing” when the personal information is disclosed for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes. You have the right to opt out of these types of disclosures of your information.

We may sell or share for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes (and may have sold or shared during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Statement) the following categories of personal information about you to online advertising services and social networks:

* Identifiers
* Commercial Information
* Online Activity
* Inferences

We do not have actual knowledge that we sell or share personal information of minors under 16 years of age.

**6\. Disclosure of Personal Information**

During the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Statement, we may have disclosed the following categories of personal information about you for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |Third Party Categories for California Consumers
| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Operating systems and platforms<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Additional Data Subject to Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80 Law | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Protected Classifications | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Commercial Information | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Biometric Information | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks<br>* [Associate Touch ID Fingertip Scan Policy and Acknowledgement](https://images.harborfreight.com/hftweb/pdfs/19-HFT-TOUCH-ID-FINGERPRINT-SCAN-POLICY.pdf) |
| Online Activity | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Geolocation data | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Sensory Information | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Employment Information | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Education Information | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |
| Inferences | * Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks |

In addition to the categories of third parties identified above, during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Statement, we may have shared personal information about you with government entities.

**7\. California Privacy Rights**

You have certain choices regarding your personal information, as described below.

* Access: You have the right to request, twice in a 12-month period, that we disclose to you the personal information we have collected, used, disclosed and sold about you during the past 12 months.
* Correction: You have the right to request that we correct the personal information we maintain about you, if that information is inaccurate.
* Deletion: You have the right to request that we delete certain personal information we have collected from you.
* Opt-Out of Sale or Sharing: You have the right to opt out of the sale of your personal information or the sharing of your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes.
* Shine the Light Request: You also may have the right to request that we provide you with (a) a list of certain categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year and (b) the identity of those third parties. Data obtained through the short code program will not be shared with any third-parties for their marketing reasons/purposes

**How to Submit a Request.** [Submit an access, correction, or deletion request](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f). To submit a Shine the Light request, please contact us in any of the ways identified in the section titled “[How to Contact Us](#contactUs)”. [Submit a request](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f) to opt out of the sale or sharing of your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes \[or limit the use and disclosure of your sensitive personal information\] or call us at 1-800-444-3353. To submit a request as an authorized agent on behalf of a consumer, click [here](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f) and choose Authorized Agent. For questions or concerns about our privacy policies and practices, please contact us as described in the “[How to Contact Us](#contactUs)” section of our Privacy & Security Policy.

**Verifying Requests.** To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your personal information or complying with your request. If you have an account with us, we may verify your identity by requiring you to sign in to your account. If you do not have an account with us and you request access to or deletion of your personal information, we may require you to provide any of the following information: first name, last name, mailing/shipping address, phone, and email address. In addition, if you do not have an account and you ask us to provide you with specific pieces of personal information, we may require you to sign a declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose personal information is the subject of the request.

**Additional Information.** If you choose to exercise any of your rights under the CCPA, you have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment by us. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may charge a reasonable fee to comply with your request.

Colorado Consumer Privacy Statement
-----------------------------------

Updated: **July 1st, 2023**

This Colorado Consumer Privacy Notice supplements the information in the Privacy and Security Policy and applies solely to Colorado consumers who interact with us in an individual or household capacity. This Colorado Notice uses certain terms that have the meaning given to them in the Colorado Privacy Act (the “CPA“).

Collection, Use and Sharing of Personal Data

We may collect, use and share personal data as described in the chart below.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |Third Party Categories for Colorado Consumers
| Category of Personal Data | Processing Purpose(s) (see full list below) | Used for Targeted Advertising? | Sold or Shared |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Contact information**, such as name, address, telephone number, screen name and email address | * Offer our products and services,<br>* Customer service functions,<br>* Create and maintain your account or membership,<br>* Promotional purposes,<br>* Contests, sweepstakes, questions or surveys<br>* Research and marketing, | **\[Yes\]** | **Not sold**<br><br>**Shared with:**<br><br>* Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Government entities |
| **Payment card information**, such as debit or credit card number | * Offer our products and services,<br>* Create and maintain your account or membership,<br>* Promotional purposes<br>* Contests, sweepstakes, questions or surveys<br>* Research and marketing, | **\[Yes\]** | **Not sold**<br><br>**Shared with:**<br><br>* Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our business partners<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Government entities |
| **Purchase history** | * Offer our products and services,<br>* Customer service functions,<br>* Promotional purposes,<br>* Contests, sweepstakes, questions or surveys<br>* Research and marketing, | **\[Yes\]** | **Not sold**<br><br>**Shared with:**<br><br>* Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Government entities |
| **Driver’s license number** | * Customer service functions, | **\[No\]** | **Not sold**<br><br>**Shared with:**<br><br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Government entities |
| **Information collected automatically**, such as cookies and web beacons, time of day, browser type and version, browser language, your operating system and platform, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet | * Offer our products and services,<br>* Promotional purposes,<br>* Contests, sweepstakes, questions or surveys<br>* Research and marketing, | **\[Yes\]** | **Not sold**<br><br>**Shared with:**<br><br>* Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks<br>* Government entities |
| **Information collected from Harbor Freight emails**, such as whether our customers have opened or forwarded those emails and/or clicked on links in those emails, customizing banner advertisements and other messages after a customer has closed the email, and determining whether a customer has made an inquiry or purchase in response to a particular email | * Offer our products and services,<br>* Customer service functions,<br>* Create and maintain your account or membership,<br>* Promotional purposes,<br>* Contests, sweepstakes, questions or surveys<br>* Research and marketing, | **\[Yes\]** | **Not sold**<br><br>**Shared with:**<br><br>* Our affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Vendors who provide services on our behalf<br>* Professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms<br>* Our joint marketing partners<br>* Our business partners<br>* Online advertising services and advertising networks<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Social networks<br>* Government entities |

Processing Purposes:

* **Offer our products and services**, such as to process your orders, to ensure proper delivery, to process returns, to better assist you when you visit or call us as well as to improve our product and service offerings
* **Customer service functions**, such as to help us promptly answer your questions and otherwise communicate with you
* **Create and maintain your account or membership**, such as registering your online account and/or club or program membership
* **Promotional purposes**, such as to send you newsletters, offers and coupons
* **Contests, sweepstakes, questions or surveys**, such as to administer your participation in a contest or sweepstakes and for Harbor Freight's other business needs, including sending you marketing communications
* **Research and marketing**, such as to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes

We do not knowingly process personal data from children under the age of 13. We also do not engage in profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning consumers, as defined in the CPA. To the extent we process deidentified information, we will maintain and use the information in deidentified form and will not attempt to reidentify the information unless permitted by applicable law.

**Your Colorado Privacy Rights**

If you are a Colorado consumer who interacts with us in an individual or household capacity (and not in a commercial or employment context), you may have the right to: (1) request access to, correction of or deletion of your personal data; and (2) opt-out of the processing of your personal data for purposes of targeted advertising or the sale of your personal data. In addition, you may have the right to obtain your personal data in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format that allows you to transmit the personal data to another entity.

How to Submit a Request

To request access to, correction of or deletion of your personal data, please click [here](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f). To opt-out of the processing of your personal data for purposes of targeted advertising or the sale of your personal data, go to the footer of our website and select the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information / Opt Out of Targeted Advertising” link, or click [here](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f).

To submit an opt-out request as an authorized agent on behalf of a consumer, please click [here](https://privacyportal-harborfreight.my.onetrust.com/webform/6071fa4d-8838-4082-b8e3-006224a42f3e/42edd688-4e60-4417-bca1-2a820290348f) and choose Authorized Agent. If you submit a request through an authorized agent, we may ask for your written permission or a power of attorney. Where you provided your authorized agent with written permission, we may require that you also verify your identity.

How We Verify Your Identity To Complete Your Requests

To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your personal information or complying with your request. If you have an account with us, we may verify your identity by requiring you to sign in to your account. If you do not have an account with us and you request access to or deletion of your personal information, we may require you to provide any of the following information: first name, last name, mailing/shipping address, phone, and email address. In addition, if you do not have an account and you ask us to provide you with specific pieces of personal information, we may require you to sign a declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose personal information is the subject of the request.

How to Submit an Appeal

You may appeal our decision with respect to a request you have submitted by sending an email to: [privacy@harborfreight.com](mailto:privacy@harborfreight.com?subject=Colorado%20Consumer%20Rights%20Appeal) with “Colorado Consumer Rights Appeal” in the subject line (must be sent from the email address used to make the Consumer Rights request).

Contact Us

For more information on how to contact us about this Colorado Consumer Privacy Notice, please see the “[How to Contact Us](#contactUs)” section of the Privacy and Security Policy.

### Security Limitations

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Harbor Freight cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us on our Sites.
